Hey guys, welcome to another video, so in previous video we have seen how to add WMIC for
persistence, the Windows management instrumentation, we have used that and we have created
a persistence mechanism, so in this video we will be seeing scheduled tasks, so I already
mentioned there is a spike kind of persistence, the fourth one will be scheduled tasks and
fifth one will be a services, so I have just mentioned in my note pad, so how to add
a scheduled task on the remote computers, because most of the malware like credential
stealers and enforce stealers, it will be using the scheduled task folders of persistence
one, so this is the simple command, you can add a persistence, so the same malware which
we are going to use, the one thing I have removed the filter consumer everything which
we have created, so now you can't able to find out the filter name like MIT and there
is no consumer, there is no consumer will be there, so here you can see only the
call, call kicks a consumer only there, so we will be also I have removed the startup
folder, so here you can find there is nothing person under the startup folder and let
me execute this command, so this is the path which we have created our malware and let
me open the session, so the port will be, the port will be 8, 7, 6, 9 I feel, let me check
yeah 8, 7, 6, 9, this is the thing which we have created our persistence mal.exe, let
me run the listener and so now the TCP listener has been activated and let me initialize
this command, scheduled task last create, so this is the command to verify whether the scheduled
task has been added, slash, we are going to create a new task and the task name and task
action, so what action we need to be executed and SC, so here you can use the specific
timing on date which on date it needs to be executed or which time it needs to execute,
so I just mentioned it is an on log on, so when we boot our machine, so our scheduled
task will be automatically get executed by Windows, let me add this, so I already mentioned,
so if you need to add any commands, any persistence, so you must be administrator privilege,
so we have seen a previous session, the privilege escalation, let me add this task, so
now the scheduled task has been successfully created, so if you are running this command
in normal user command Chrome we will be getting a error like access denied, and here
you can find the scheduled task has been added successfully in the administrator console,
in the administrator command Chrome, and let me verify the scheduled task, whether it was
still present on the, whether it was created properly, let me check that, so here you can
find the meta-
operator task name that has been successfully created and status was ready to run, and
we will be, the next command will be the scheduled task delete if you need to delete
this specific task, you can use the command to delete that task, okay, so I already started
my listener, let me restart my Windows machine, and I will check whether it was executing
or not, so we will wait for a few minutes, let my Windows will be back to form, so let
me, let's see, so now the Windows machine has been started, so let me give a password,
okay, so now here you can see, so before it gets started, my scheduled task has been loaded
up, and I'll be executing a connection from the target machine, so here you can find, and
my machine also has been started, okay, this is the, one of a really good way to add a
persistence mechanism in Windows machine, okay, so I can use shell, and let me, okay, let
me check who am I slash all, so here you can find our privilege will be a high mandatory
level, but when we adding it in a, WMI, we'll be getting a system mandatory level of privilege,
so here we'll easily got a high mandatory level, okay, so this is the way you can add a
persistence mechanism in Windows machine, so based on a scheduled task, okay, so let's
excite, exit this window, and so here you can see a command to delete a scheduled task, we'll
ask in delete or successfully, so let me re verify whether we have a task with the same
name or not, let me check that, so the system cannot find a specified file that task has
been successfully removed, so this turn off away, you can easily create a scheduled task and
you can exploit an animation, okay, so thanks guys for watching this, and I hope you have
a clear understanding about the scheduled task, we will hop off and we will see you guys
in the next video, thank you, bye bye.